Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Papyri Fragments, 55 Linear Feet in 44 small flat boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.25, cuid31006; 27 fragments 06 x 3 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.25)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.26, cuid31007; 27 fragments 03.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.26)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.27, cuid31008; 27 fragments 01.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.27)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.01, cuid31009; 43 fragments 04.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.02, cuid31010; 43 fragments 01.5 x 4 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.03, cuid31011; 43 fragments 03.5 x 3 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.04, cuid31012; 43 fragments 05 x 2 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.05, cuid31013; 43 fragments 01.5 x 1 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.06, cuid31014; 43 fragments 04.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.07, cuid31015; 43 fragments 04.5 x 3 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.08, cuid31016; 43 fragments 05 x 2.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.09, cuid31017; 43 fragments 02 x 3 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.10, cuid31018; 43 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.11, cuid31019; 43 fragments 02 x 2 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.12, cuid31020; 43 fragments 02.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.13, cuid31021; 43 fragments 02.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.14, cuid31022; 43 fragments 03 x 1.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.15, cuid31023; 43 fragments 04.5 x 4 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.16, cuid31024; 43 fragments 08 x 3.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.17, cuid31025; 43 fragments 01.5 x 3 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.18, cuid31026; 43 fragments 03 x 1 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.19, cuid31027; 43 fragments 04.5 x 1 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.20, cuid31028; 43 fragments 08 x 3.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.20)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.21, cuid31029; 43 fragments 03 x 5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.21)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.22, cuid31030; 43 fragments 03 x 1 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.22)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.23, cuid31031; 43 fragments 03 x 1 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.23)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.24, cuid31032; 43 fragments 04.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.24)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.25, cuid31033; 43 fragments 05.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.25)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.26, cuid31034; 43 fragments 08 x 2 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.26)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.27, cuid31035; 43 fragments 04 x 2 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.27)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.28, cuid31036; 43 fragments 02 x 2 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.28)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.29, cuid31037; 43 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.29)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.31, cuid31038; 43 fragments 04 x 3 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0533.31)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.32, cuid31039; 43 fragments 06 x 3.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0533.32)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.33, cuid31040; 43 fragments 01.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0533.33)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.34, cuid31041; 43 fragments 06 x 2 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0533.34)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.35, cuid31042; 43 fragments 2.5 x 0.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0533.35)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.36, cuid31043; 43 fragments 02 x 1.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0533.36)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.37, cuid31044; 43 fragments 04 x 2.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0533.37)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.38, cuid31045; 43 fragments 05.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0533.38)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.39, cuid31046; 43 fragments 04 x 2.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0533.39)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.40, cuid31047; 43 fragments 11 x 2.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0533.40)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.41, cuid31048; 43 fragments 05 x 2 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0533.41)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.42, cuid31049; 43 fragments 07 x 1.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0533.42)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0533.43, cuid31050; 43 fragments 04.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0533.43)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.01, cuid31051; 24 fragments 07.5 x 7 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.02, cuid31052; 24 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.03, cuid31053; 24 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.04, cuid31054; 24 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.05, cuid31055; 24 fragments 03.5 x 3 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.06, cuid31056; 24 fragments 00.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.07, cuid31057; 24 fragments 04 x 3 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.08, cuid31058; 24 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.09, cuid31059; 24 fragments 04.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.10, cuid31060; 24 fragments 02 x 2 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.11, cuid31061; 24 fragments 04.5 x 2 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.12, cuid31062; 24 fragments 02 x 2 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.13, cuid31063; 24 fragments 01.5 x 3 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.14, cuid31064; 24 fragments 10 x 3.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.15, cuid31065; 24 fragments 09 x 2 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.16, cuid31066; 24 fragments 07 x 3.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.17, cuid31067; 24 fragments 04 x 4 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.18, cuid31068; 24 fragments 04 x 1.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.19, cuid31069; 24 fragments 09 x 3 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.20, cuid31070; 24 fragments 06 x 4 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.20)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.21, cuid31071; 24 fragments 01 x 10 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.21)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.22, cuid31072; 24 fragments 06 x 10.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.22)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.23, cuid31073; 24 fragments 06 x 2 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.23)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0534.24, cuid31074; 24 fragments 05.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0534.24)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.01, cuid31075; 16 fragments 13 x 3 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.02, cuid31076; 16 fragments 08 x 5.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.03, cuid31077; 16 fragments 07 x 8 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.04, cuid31078; 16 fragments 09.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.05, cuid31079; 16 fragments 07 x 5.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.06, cuid31080; 16 fragments 13 x 6.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.07, cuid31081; 16 fragments 02.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.08, cuid31082; 16 fragments 05 x 4.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.09, cuid31083; 16 fragments 07.5 x 3 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.10, cuid31084; 16 fragments 06.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.11, cuid31085; 16 fragments 04.5 x 4 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.12, cuid31086; 16 fragments 02 x 3 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.13, cuid31087; 16 fragments 04 x 3 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.14, cuid31088; 16 fragments 08 x 2 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.15, cuid31089; 16 fragments 05 x 4.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.16, cuid31090; 16 fragments 03.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.01, cuid31091; 19 fragments 08.2 x 2.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0536.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.02, cuid31092; 19 fragments 12.5 x 2 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0536.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.03, cuid31093; 19 fragments 04.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0536.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.04, cuid31094; 19 fragments 05 x 2.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0536.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.05, cuid31095; 19 fragments 03.5 x 1 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0536.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.06, cuid31096; 19 fragments 08 x 6.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0536.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.07, cuid31097; 19 fragments 09 x 6 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0536.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.08, cuid31098; 19 fragments 05.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.09, cuid31099; 19 fragments 07 x 1.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.10, cuid31100; 19 fragments 03.5 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.11, cuid31101; 19 fragments 03 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.12, cuid31102; 19 fragments 05.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.13, cuid31103; 19 fragments 02 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.14, cuid31104; 19 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.15, cuid31105; 19 fragments 07.5 x 11.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.17, cuid31106; 19 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.18, cuid31107; 19 fragments 02 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.19, cuid31108; 19 fragments 02.5 x 00.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.01, cuid31109; 35 fragments 07 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.02, cuid31110; 35 fragments 04 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.03, cuid31111; 35 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.05, cuid31112; 35 fragments 04 x 10.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.06, cuid31113; 35 fragments 07 x 5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.07, cuid31114; 35 fragments 05 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.08, cuid31115; 35 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.09, cuid31116; 35 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.10, cuid31117; 35 fragments 06.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.11, cuid31118; 35 fragments 06.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.12, cuid31119; 35 fragments 04 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.13, cuid31120; 35 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.14, cuid31121; 35 fragments 05 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.15, cuid31122; 35 fragments 06.5 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.16, cuid31123; 35 fragments 09.5 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.17, cuid31124; 35 fragments 03 x 0.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.18, cuid31125; 35 fragments 08 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.19, cuid31126; 35 fragments 03.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.20, cuid31127; 35 fragments 04 x 4 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.20)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.21, cuid31128; 35 fragments 06.5 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.21)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.22, cuid31129; 35 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.22)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.23, cuid31130; 35 fragments 02.5 x 4 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.23)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.24, cuid31131; 35 fragments 05 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.24)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.25, cuid31132; 35 fragments 02.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.25)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.26, cuid31133; 35 fragments 04.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.26)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.27, cuid31134; 35 fragments 03.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.27)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.28, cuid31135; 35 fragments 03.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.28)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.29, cuid31136; 35 fragments 03.5 x 04 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.29)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.30, cuid31137; 35 fragments 06 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.30)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.31, cuid31138; 35 fragments 05.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.31)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.32, cuid31139; 35 fragments 01.5 x 1 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.32)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.33, cuid31140; 35 fragments 04.5 x 4 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.33)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.34, cuid31141; 35 fragments 04 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.34)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.35, cuid31142; 35 fragments 05.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.35)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.01, cuid31143; 33 fragments 05.5 x 6 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.02, cuid31144; 33 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.03, cuid31145; 33 fragments 02.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.04, cuid31146; 33 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.05, cuid31147; 33 fragments 02 x 3.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.06, cuid31148; 33 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.07, cuid31149; 33 fragments 02.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.08, cuid31150; 33 fragments 03.5 x 4 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.09, cuid31151; 33 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.10, cuid31152; 33 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.11, cuid31153; 33 fragments 04.5 x 5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.12, cuid31154; 33 fragments 05 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.13, cuid31155; 33 fragments 02 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.14, cuid31156; 33 fragments 01.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.15, cuid31157; 33 fragments 09.5 x 17.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.17, cuid31158; 33 fragments 06.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.18, cuid31159; 33 fragments 02 x 0.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.19, cuid31160; 33 fragments 03 x 4.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.20, cuid31161; 33 fragments 11.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.20)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.21, cuid31162; 33 fragments 02.5 x 1 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.21)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.22, cuid31163; 33 fragments 02.5 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.22)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.23, cuid31164; 33 fragments 04.5 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.23)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.24, cuid31165; 33 fragments 02 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.24)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.25, cuid31166; 33 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.25)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.26, cuid31167; 33 fragments 02.5 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.26)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.27, cuid31168; 33 fragments 01 x 6 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.27)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.28, cuid31169; 33 fragments 02.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.28)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.29, cuid31170; 33 fragments 03 x 2.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.29)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.30, cuid31171; 33 fragments 03.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.30)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.31, cuid31172; 33 fragments 06 x 9 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.31)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.32, cuid31173; 33 fragments 03 x 1 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.32)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.33, cuid31174; 33 fragments 04.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.33)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.01, cuid31175; 19 fragments 11.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.02, cuid31176; 19 fragments 07.5 x 5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.03, cuid31177; 19 fragments 02.5 x 9.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.05, cuid31178; 19 fragments 10 x 10 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.07, cuid31179; 19 fragments 02.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.08, cuid31180; 19 fragments 01.5 x 4 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.10, cuid31181; 19 fragments 01 x 5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.11, cuid31182; 19 fragments 01.5 x 7 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.12, cuid31183; 19 fragments 03 x 4 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.15, cuid31184; 19 fragments 06 x 6.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.16, cuid31185; 19 fragments 07.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.17, cuid31186; 19 fragments 06 x 4.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.18, cuid31187; 19 fragments 06 x 6 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.19, cuid31188; 19 fragments 06.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.01, cuid31189; 18 fragments 07.5 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.02, cuid31190; 18 fragments 2.5 x 12 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.03, cuid31191; 18 fragments 06 x 5.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.04, cuid31192; 18 fragments 00.5 x 0.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.05, cuid31193; 18 fragments 05.5 x 2 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.06, cuid31194; 18 fragments 11.5 x 6 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.07, cuid31195; 18 fragments 02 x 6.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.08, cuid31196; 18 fragments 05 x 4.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.09, cuid31197; 18 fragments 01 x 4.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.10, cuid31198; 18 fragments 03 x 4 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.11, cuid31199; 18 fragments 04 x 7 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.12, cuid31200; 18 fragments 02 x 1 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.13, cuid31201; 18 fragments 03.5 x 4 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.14, cuid31202; 18 fragments 04 x 2 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.15, cuid31203; 18 fragments 03 x 6.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.16, cuid31204; 18 fragments 03.5 x 4 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.17, cuid31205; 18 fragments 04 x 10.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.18, cuid31206; 18 fragments 05 x 6 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.01, cuid31207; 19 fragments 08 x 3.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.02, cuid31208; 19 fragments 03.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.03, cuid31209; 19 fragments 03 x 4 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.04, cuid31210; 19 fragments 06 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.05, cuid31211; 19 fragments 06 x 4 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.06, cuid31212; 19 fragments 04 x 3.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.07, cuid31213; 19 fragments 09 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.08, cuid31214; 19 fragments 04.5 x 6 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.09, cuid31215; 19 fragments 02.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.10, cuid31216; 19 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.11, cuid31217; 19 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.12, cuid31218; 19 fragments 06.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.13, cuid31219; 19 fragments 05 x 2.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0541.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.14, cuid31220; 19 fragments 03.5 x 6 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0541.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.15, cuid31221; 19 fragments 08 x 3 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0541.15)